next we'll take a look at some of the
接下来我们来看看一些
basics of navigating the user interface
导航用户界面的基础知识
in order to ensure the canvas is
为了确保画布
centered and visible on the screen click
居中并在屏幕上可见点击
on the percentage menu in the overview
在概述中的百分比菜单上
panel and choose fit view should the
面板 并选择适合视图 如果
canvas become angled there's a button
画布变得有角度了 有一个按钮
here to reset the rotation as well right
在这里重置旋转也是对的
click and choose reset using a pen or a
单击并选择重置使用钢笔或
mouse you can hover over many of the
鼠标你可以将鼠标悬停在许多
buttons in cre and see a tool tip that
按钮并查看工具提示 该工具提示
indicates what each feature is you'll
指明每个功能是什么 您将
notice that once I click on a button or
请注意 一旦我点击一个按钮或
menu it is highlighted in blue this is
菜单以蓝色突出显示 这是
how you can tell if a tool brush feature
如何判断工具画笔功能
or setting is active or not now let's
或者设置现在是否处于活动状态 让我们
try making some marks on the canvas with
试着在画布上画些记号
brushes the tool box has all of the
笔刷工具箱中包含所有
tools that you'll be using here in Crea
您将在Crea中使用的工具
and each tool can perform a variety of
并且每种工具都可以执行各种
functions for example we can select the
函数 例如 我们可以选择
freehand brush tool which tells Crea
写意画笔工具 告诉Crea
that we are ready to paint if the brush
我们已经准备好了 如果画笔
tool is not selected we will not be able
未选择工具 我们将无法
to paint on our canvas next let's make
为了在我们的画布上作画 接下来让我们做
sure we have a visible color selected
当然 我们已经选择了可见的颜色
for paint painting it's hard to see what
对于油漆来说 很难看出什么是
you're doing if you're using white paint
如果你使用白色油漆 你会做什么？
on a white canvas so let's choose dark
在白色画布上 所以让我们选择黑色
blue for now this way we can easily see
现在是蓝色的 这样我们就很容易看到
The Strokes we're making as we paint to
当我们作画时 我们正在进行的笔触
choose a color click inside a section of
在的一部分内选择一种颜色点击
the circular artistic color selector to
圆形艺术颜色选择器
select a hue and
选择一个色调 然后
saturation next choose the brightness
饱和度下一步选择亮度
you want from the strip on the left if
如果您想从左边的条带中选择
you prefer a more standard way of
你更喜欢一种更标准的方式
choosing color you can toggle to the
选择您可以切换到
wide gamut color selector or choose from
宽域颜色选择器或从中选择
a palette of swatches we're going to go
我们要做的一组色板
more in depth into the color selection
更深入地了解颜色选择
options later you may have already
以后您可能已经有了选项
selected a brush so to make sure we're
选择了一把刷子 以确保我们
all working with the same brush let's go
都是同一把刷子我们走吧
to the brush presets on the left and
添加到左侧的笔刷预设和
choose the paint category to filter out
选择要过滤掉的油漆类别
only those brushes I'll choose the basic
只有那些刷子 我会选择基本的
five size opacity brush and if I paint a
五个大小的不透明度画笔 如果我绘制一个
test stroke using firm pressure I get a
使用坚定的压力测试冲程我得到一个
fairly simple stroke shape with paint
用油漆画出相当简单的笔触形状
that is flat and opaque if you're using
它是平坦和不透明的 如果你使用
a drawing tablet you can control the
一款绘图板 您可以控制
thickness opacity and other properties
厚度不透明度和其他属性
of your brushes by adjus adjusting the
通过调整笔刷的
amount of pressure you apply for example
例如 你施加的压力量
light pressure will create thinner more
轻压会产生更多的稀薄
transparent lines while heavier pressure
透明线条 压力更大
will result in thicker more opaque lines
将导致更粗、更不透明的线条
it's worth noting that a mouse doesn't
值得注意的是 老鼠并不
have this capability and can't replicate
有这种能力 不能复制
this effect now that we've made a mess
现在我们把事情搞得一团糟
on our canvas let's learn how to quickly
在我们的画布上 让我们学习如何快速
clear everything off of course you can
当然你可以清理掉所有的东西
use your eraser but there's a faster way
用你的橡皮擦 但有一种更快的方法
to do it simply press delete to clear
要执行此操作 只需按Delete以清除
the contents of the currently selected
当前选定的
layer now that we are able to paint
层 现在我们可以绘制
paint on our canvas let's go more in
在我们的画布上作画让我们再深入一些
depth into the navigation tools we'll
深入了解导航工具 我们将
start with panting the canvas or moving
从在画布上喘气或移动开始
the canvas around your workspace you can
工作区周围的画布 您可以
do that in a number of different ways
要做到这一点 有很多不同的方法
the first is to use the overview panel
第一种方法是使用概述面板
you may need to expand it vertically
您可能需要垂直展开它
when you click and hold with your mouse
当你用鼠标点击并按住时
or tap and hold with your pen on the
或者用您的钢笔在
thumbnail of your canvas you can drag to
您可以拖动到的画布缩略图
reposition it another way to pan is to
重新定位平移的另一种方式是
hold down the space bar on a keyboard
按住键盘上的空格键
that will toggle your cursor to the pan
这会将您的光标切换到平移
mode allowing you to move moove the
模式 允许您移动移动
canvas releasing space bar returns you
画布释放空格键返回您
to whatever tool was previously selected
之前选择的任何工具
if you're using a touch capable device
如果您使用的是支持触摸的设备
you can also press down with two fingers
你也可以用两个手指按下
and drag your canvas to pan it around
然后拖动你的画布来平移它
try to avoid twisting or rotating your
尽量避免扭动或旋转你的
fingers because it will rotate your
手指 因为它会旋转你的
canvas if that happens and your canvas
画布 如果发生这种情况 你的画布
is a skew you can right click in the
是一种倾斜 您可以在
overview panel to return the canvas to
要将画布返回到的概述面板
its upright position there are also
它的直立位置在那里也有
Options under settings configure Crea
设置配置创建下的选项
canvas input settings to customize touch
画布输入设置以自定义触摸
Rec ignition if you don't want it to
如果你不想让它点火 那就重新启动
affect the rotation of the canvas
影响画布的旋转
multi-touch can be temporarily disabled
可以暂时禁用多点触控
using a switch or a button on your
使用计算机上的开关或按钮
tablet so if it's not working be sure to
所以 如果它不起作用 一定要
check that next let's take a look at
接下来我们来看一看
zooming in and out of the canvas we can
放大和缩小画布 我们可以
do that in a number of different ways
要做到这一点 有很多不同的方法
first I can do it with the menu and
首先 我可以用菜单做 然后
slider in the overview panel another way
概述面板中的滑块以另一种方式
to do it is to hold Control Plus space
要做到这一点 请按住Control Plus空间
bar on your keyboard and click or tap
键盘上的按键 然后单击或轻触
and drag left or right or up and down on
并向左或向右或向上和向下拖动
the canvas this will let you focus on on
这将让您专注于画布
a Target area this method utilizes
此方法利用的目标区域
scrubby Zoom which lets you zoom in and
SCRUBY缩放 允许您放大和
out very fluidly the other modes Zoom to
将其他模式非常流畅地放大到
specific increments another way to zoom
特定增量是缩放的另一种方式
in increments is to use the keyboard
递增的是使用键盘
shortcuts of plus and minus you're not
加和减的快捷方式你不是
limited to navigating with your keyboard
仅限于使用键盘导航
you can also use the express keys on
您也可以使用快捷键
your tablet to invoke these tools and
您的平板电脑来调用这些工具和
commands I'll explain how to use express
命令我将解释如何使用Express
Keys later in this lesson we can also
在本课后面的部分中 我们还可以
zoom using touch gestures by spreading
通过展开使用触摸手势进行缩放
two fingers apart to zoom in or bringing
分开两个手指来放大或带上
two fingers closer together to zoom out
两个手指靠得更近以缩小图像
there are also options in the overview
概述中还提供了一些选项
panel to fit the image on the screen and
面板以适合屏幕上的图像 并且
zoom the canvas to 100% 100% means the
将画布缩放到100%100%表示
canvas is not zoomed in or zoomed out
画布未放大或缩小
and after zooming in you can drag the
放大后 您可以拖动
box over the thumbnail to focus on
要关注的缩略图上的方框
specific areas of your painting to
您的绘画的特定区域
rotate the canvas you can use the
旋转画布您可以使用
overview panel or the shortcuts hold
概述面板或按住快捷键
shift plus space bar then drag to rotate
Shift+空格键 然后拖动以旋转
the canvas around a central axis
围绕中轴线的画布
likewise you can also press four or six
同样 您也可以按4或6
to rotate in increments five will reset
要以增量旋转 五个将重置
the rotation you can also manually set
您还可以手动设置旋转
the rotation angle from the overview
总览中的旋转角度
panel for example you could rotate the
例如 您可以旋转面板
canvas
帆布
45° you can also use Touch to rotate the
45°您也可以使用触摸来旋转
canvas by twisting two fingers you may
通过扭动两个手指 你可以
accidentally paint while touching with
在触摸时不小心画了
one finger so you may want to disable
一根手指 所以您可能想要禁用
that in the Creed preferences under
在下面的信条首选项中
General
一般信息
tools once you have mastered these
一旦你掌握了这些工具
navigation tools it's quite easy to
导航工具可以很容易地
manipulate your view of the canvas
操纵您的画布视图
if you have a drawing tablet it may come
如果你有绘图板 它可能会来
with Express Keys these are buttons that
使用快捷键时 这些按钮
are built into the device and can be
都内置于设备中 并且可以
customized to perform keyboard shortcuts
自定义以执行键盘快捷键
and execute commands with encr they can
并使用ENCR执行命令 他们可以
be a useful tool for streamlining your
成为简化您工作流程的有用工具
workflow and for saving time I'm using
为了节省我使用的工作流程和时间
the centiq 27 QHD touch which comes with
配备Centiq 27 QHD触控
the walkom express key remote if I open
如果我打开Walkom Express键遥控器
the walkom tablet properties I can click
我可以点击的Walkom平板电脑属性
on the express key remote or whichever
在快捷键遥控器或其他任何键上
device that I want to configure it's
我想要配置的设备
very important that you make a note of
非常重要的一点是你要记下
which application that you're assigning
您要分配的是哪个应用程序
commands to by default all other is
默认情况下 所有其他命令为
selected which is a global setting for
选定 这是的全局设置
all
全
applications that Global setting can be
全局设置可以是的应用程序
overwritten by adding specific
通过添加特定内容覆盖
applications once you choose a specific
一旦您选择了特定的
application you can have different
您可以使用不同的应用程序
shortcuts for each individual
每个人的快捷方式
application to add an application click
要添加应用程序的应用程序点击
on the plus button I'll choose the cre
在加号按钮上 我将选择cre
application so that the functions I
应用程序 以使函数
program will apply only to Crea then
该计划将仅适用于Crea
I'll click on Crea to activate it I
我将点击Crea将其激活
won't go into detail about how to set
不会详细说明如何设置
this up but you can experiment to
但你可以试验一下
determine which tools and commands you
确定您需要使用哪些工具和命令
use frequently enough to justify
频繁使用足以证明
assigning them to an Express key your
将它们分配给您的快捷键
pen may also have buttons that you can
笔也可能有按钮 您可以
assign shortcuts to these buttons are
为这些按钮指定的快捷键是
usually located near the tip of the pen
通常位于笔尖附近
typically Pens have one two or three
通常 钢笔有一个、两个或三个
buttons to give you an example you could
按钮来给你一个例子 你可以
program one of these pens to act as the
对其中一支钢笔进行编程以充当
Eraser allowing you to erase by holding
橡皮擦 你可以通过按住擦除
down the pen button next I want to
按下钢笔按钮下一步我想
discuss some of the panels that are
讨论以下几个小组
floating here in our interface we can
在我们的界面中浮动在这里 我们可以
have individual panels floating on our
让各个面板漂浮在我们的
screen like this or we can have these
像这样的屏幕 或者我们可以有这些
panels grouped together in different
组合在不同位置的配电盘
ways panels or Dockers as they referred
他们所指的方式面板或码头工人
to in cre can be collapsed so that they
可以折叠到Cre中以便它们
take up less space on the screen or they
在屏幕上占用更少的空间 或者
can be opened when it's time to access
可以在需要访问时打开
the contents within you can drag panels
您可以拖动面板中的内容
around and reposition them by dragging
通过拖动来绕过并重新定位它们
from the top bar of the panel if the
从面板的顶栏 如果
panel has an X and you click on it
面板上有一个X 您可以点击它
you'll close the panel you can restore
您将关闭您可以恢复的面板
panels from settings Dockers I'll
Dockers的设置面板我会
restore the overview panel you can
恢复概述面板 您可以
navigate between the different panels
在不同的面板之间导航
that are grouped together by clicking on
通过单击将它们分组在一起
the tab many panels also have one or
选项卡多个面板也有一个或
more options buttons that can customize
可自定义更多选项按钮
the panel contents panels can be docked
可以停靠面板内容面板
together on the sides of the UI but not
一起出现在用户界面的两侧 而不是
when they are free floating you can even
当它们自由漂浮时 您甚至可以
dock panels on the top and bottom of the
顶部和底部的停靠面板
UI to resize panels and reveal more or
用于调整面板大小并显示更多内容的用户界面
less of their contents drag from the
较少的内容从
sides or corners of the panel some
面板的侧边或边角
panels have content that will scale in
面板包含可扩展的内容
relation to the panel the color selector
与面板的关系颜色选择器
is one such example
就是这样一个例子
as I mentioned earlier panels can even
正如我之前提到的那样 小组甚至可以
be locked if you're concerned about
如果你担心的话请锁定
accidentally moving the panels while
不小心移动了电池板
you're drawing you can unlock the panels
你在画画 你可以解锁面板
with the same button another way to
使用相同的按钮以另一种方式
navigate is to use the pop-up panel you
导航是使用弹出式面板
can access this whenever the brush tool
无论何时使用画笔工具都可以访问它
is selected by right clicking on the
通过右击
canvas on the outside are controls to
外部的画布是控件 用于
rotate the canvas and zoom there are
旋转画布并进行缩放
more controls here that we will explore
我们将在这里探索更多控件
later I'm using a fairly large display
后来 我使用了一个相当大的显示器
which allows me to keep a wide view of
这让我可以保持一个宽广的视野
my canvas this while still having room
我的画布这还有空间
for multiple panels your workflow may
对于多个面板 您的工作流程可能
require even more panels in which case
在这种情况下需要更多的面板
it can be helpful to hide the interface
隐藏界面会很有帮助
so that you only see the canvas you can
这样你只能看到你能看到的画布
do this by pressing tab on your keyboard
按键盘上的Tab键即可完成此操作
This removes a lot of the distractions
这消除了很多分心的事情
and allows you to focus on your painting
让你专注于你的画
if you want the panels to return press
如果您想让面板返回 请按
tab again it's easy enough to press tab
再次按Tab键很容易
on your keyboard but you can also set an
在键盘上 但您也可以设置
Express key to show and hide the UI if
Express键显示和隐藏UI 如果
you want to squeeze a tiny bit more room
你想挤多一点空间
out of C's UI you can enter full screen
从C的UI中可以进入全屏
mode from The View menu and that will
从“查看”菜单中的模式 这将
hide the application bar near the top of
隐藏顶部附近的应用程序栏
the screen this can be useful if you're
如果您是
concerned about accidentally closing the
担心不小心关闭
application or moving the window to exit
应用程序或移动窗口退出
full screen mode you'll have to click on
您必须单击全屏模式
it again in the view menu or you can use
在视图菜单中再次显示 或者您可以使用
the control shift F keyboard shortcut to
控制换档F键盘快捷方式到
make it easier to invoke those were the
使其更容易援引那些
basics of navigating the UI andr in the
在中导航UI和r的基础知识
next lesson I'll give you an overview of
下一课我将向您概述
how to select
如何选择
brushes
刷子